[
  {
    "question": "Which is the closest planet to the SUN?",
    "options": [
      "jupiter",
      "mercury",
      "mars"
    ],
    "correct": "mercury"
  },
  {
    "question": "For every 2 orbit of the sun, mercury completes___________rotation about its axis.",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a century how many times the mercury can be observed from the earth?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "10",
      "11"
    ],
    "correct": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Diameter of the planet is?",
    "options": [
      "<2000",
      "<3500",
      "<5000"
    ],
    "correct": "<5000"
  },
  {
    "question": "Orbit period according to earth days is?",
    "options": [
      "90",
      "88",
      "87"
    ],
    "correct": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "Your weight on mercury will be ______percent of yours on earth.",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "40",
      "37"
    ],
    "correct": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "A day on mercury lasts ______  earth days.",
    "options": [
      "166",
      "176",
      "186"
    ],
    "correct": "176"
  },
  {
    "question": "Distance from sun is about _________km.",
    "options": [
      "35-40 million",
      "46-70 million",
      "84-93 million"
    ],
    "correct": "46-70 million"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mercury is the ____ densest planet.",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mercury has ______ core.",
    "options": [
      "molten",
      "solid",
      "gas"
    ],
    "correct": "molten"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mercury has wrinkles calles as _______.",
    "options": [
      "mobate scarps",
      "lobate scarps",
      "cobate scarps"
    ],
    "correct": "lobate scarps"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mercury is the second ______ planet.",
    "options": [
      "coldest",
      "hottest",
      "humid"
    ],
    "correct": "hottest"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many spacecrafts have visited mercury?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mercury is named after the _________ messanger.",
    "options": [
      "roman",
      "greek",
      "asian"
    ],
    "correct": "roman"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mercury is mainly composed of ___________ and ________.",
    "options": [
      "sand and stones.",
      "rocks and mud.",
      "heavy metal and rocks."
    ],
    "correct": "heavy metal and rocks."
  }
]